(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-05T08:15:49.105230",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
最近行ったのよ カラオケ
I went to karaoke recently...
何さ
You know,
2時間で解散って思うじゃん そっからなのよ
you'd think it's over in two hours, but that's when it starts!
え？
Huh?
いろんなことできるわけ？
You can do all sorts of things?
やばいぞ！
It's wild!
X PARK最高！
X PARK is the best!
ふくや
Fukuya
明太子が
Mentaiko...
明太子が生まれ変わる新しい技を編み出しました！
Has devised a new technique for the rebirth of mentaiko!
行きます！ふくやの明太子から生まれためんチーズシリーズ！
Here we go! The Men-Cheese series born from Fukuya's mentaiko!
ピリリな味わい まことも大好き！
A spicy flavor Mako loves too!
詳しくはWebで！
Details on the Web!
ここが限界？ 誰のセリフ？
Is this the limit? Whose line is that?
テンプレな煽り文句じゃ
With template provocation lines,
no flinch no flinch
届きもしない
not even reaching it.
it's up to me
お・わ・か・り？
Understand?
hey go！ ただ 夢中に move on
Hey go! Just moving on, absorbed in it,
進む 私を 誰も
advancing, nobody can
止められやしない (come here)
stop me (come here).
壁は 高ければ 高い方がいい
The higher the wall, the better!
i just need to get better
get the crown (hey！)
get the crown (hey!)
with these hands
用意された 頂じゃものたんない
The prepared summit isn't enough!
stand up (hey！)
stand up (hey!)
even if fall
昨日の 自分に 興味はない
I have no interest in yesterday's self!
looking to the future
私たちが 創り出す (beyond the world)
What we create (beyond the world)
栄光を目指すだけ
is just aiming for glory!
get the crown (hey！)
get the crown (hey!)
with these hands (overflow overflow)
抑えきれない
Unable to suppress it,
majesty of a stars
高まってん tension
tension rising high,
がなる distortion
roaring distortion,
エリア extension
area extension!
get out get out get out get out get out！
get out get out get out get out get out!
苦しいの 辛いのか怖いのかわ so easy
Suffering, pain, fear... so easy!
痛いの？ no thank you
Pain? No thank you.
trace なんかしたって useless
Tracing along is just useless!
誰かの奴じゃ全然楽しくない (boredom)
Someone else's way isn't fun at all (boredom).
誰も知らない世界を見せてあげる
I'll show you a world nobody knows!
let's start a revolution
get the crown (hey！)
get the crown (hey!)
with these hands
用意された 頂じゃものたんない
The prepared summit isn't enough!
stand up (hey！)
stand up (hey!)
even if fall
昨日の 自分に 興味はない
I have no interest in yesterday's self!
looking to the future
誰かを蹴落とし手にした栄光
Glory gained by kicking others down—
仮初のエクスタシーじゃ意味ない
fleeting ecstasy means nothing!
fighting myself 貫き
Pushing through, fighting myself,
その先にしかない crown
the crown is only found beyond that!
late 遅すぎ after dark
Too late, after dark.
舞台は常にスポットライトの下よ (attention)
The stage is always under the spotlight (attention)!
ついておいでここからが show time turn it up！
Follow me, the show time starts here, turn it up!
get the crown (hey！)
get the crown (hey!)
with these hands
そこら辺の椅子なんてどうでもいい
Chairs around here don't matter at all!
stand up (hey！)
stand up (hey!)
even if fall
ほら玉座がよく似合うでしょ
See? The throne suits me well, right?
the arrival of the true queen
甘い誘惑乗りこなし (top of the world)
Riding past sweet temptations (top of the world),
想像のその先へ
heading beyond imagination!
get the crown (hey！)
get the crown (hey!)
with these hands (overflow overflow)
解き放て
Unleash it,
majesty of a stars
get the crown (hey！)
get the crown (hey!)
with these hands
用意された 頂じゃものたんない
The prepared summit isn't enough!
stand up (hey！)
stand up (hey!)
even if fall
昨日の 自分に 興味はない
I have no interest in yesterday's self!
looking to the future
私たちが 創り出す (beyond the world)
What we create (beyond the world)
栄光を目指すだけ
is just aiming for glory!
get the crown (hey！)
get the crown (hey!)
with these hands (overflow overflow)
抑えきれない
Unable to suppress it,
majesty of a stars
高まってん tension
tension rising high,
がなる distortion
roaring distortion,
エリア extension
area extension!
get out get out get out get out get out！
get out get out get out get out get out!
苦しいの 辛いのか怖いのかわ so easy
Suffering, pain, fear... so easy!
痛いの？ no thank you
Pain? No thank you.
trace なんかしたって useless
Tracing along is just useless!
誰かの奴じゃ全然楽しくない (boredom)
Someone else's way isn't fun at all (boredom).
誰も知らない世界を見せてあげる
I'll show you a world nobody knows!
let's start a revolution
get the crown (hey！)
get the crown (hey!)
with these hands
用意された 頂じゃものたんない
The prepared summit isn't enough!
stand up (hey！)
stand up (hey!)
even if fall
昨日の 自分に 興味はない
I have no interest in yesterday's self!
looking to the future
誰かを蹴落とし手にした栄光
Glory gained by kicking others down—
仮初のエクスタシーじゃ意味ない
fleeting ecstasy means nothing!
fighting myself 貫き
Pushing through, fighting myself,
その先にしかない crown
the crown is only found beyond that!
late 遅すぎ after dark
Too late, after dark.
舞台は常にスポットライトの下よ (attention)
The stage is always under the spotlight (attention)!
ついておいでここからが show time turn it up！
Follow me, the show time starts here, turn it up!
get the crown (hey！)
get the crown (hey!)
with these hands
そこら辺の椅子なんてどうでもいい
Chairs around here don't matter at all!
stand up (hey！)
stand up (hey!)
even if fall
ほら玉座がよく似合うでしょ
See? The throne suits me well, right?
the arrival of the true queen
甘い誘惑乗りこなし (top of the world)
Riding past sweet temptations (top of the world),
想像のその先へ
heading beyond imagination!
get the crown (hey！)
get the crown (hey!)
with these hands (overflow overflow)
解き放て
Unleash it,
majesty of a stars
本日、星街すいせいライブツアー 2024
Thank you very much for attending today's
『Spectra of Nova』にご来場いただき誠にありがとうございます。
Hoshimachi Suisei Live Tour 2024 "Spectra of Nova".
星街すいせい です！
I'm Hoshimachi Suisei!
最後までライブをお楽しみいただくために、いくつかご案内させていただきます。
To ensure everyone enjoys the concert until the very end, we have a few announcements to make.
公演中の撮影、録音、録画機材の使用は固くお断りいたします。
The use of recording, photographing, and video equipment during the performance is strictly prohibited.
万が一、具合が悪くなってしまった場合は無理をせず、近くのスタッフへおしらせください。
Should you feel unwell, please do not overexert yourself and notify nearby staff.
会場内での、モッシュ、ダイブ、ステージに物を投げ込む、タコヤキを食べるなどなど、他のみんなの迷惑になったり、公演を妨げる行為は一切禁止です。
Inside the venue, moshing, diving, throwing objects on stage, eating takoyaki, and other disruptive acts are strictly prohibited.
ルールを守って盛り上がってくださいね！
Please follow the rules and enjoy yourselves!
いいお返事！
Good response!
また、本公演は映像配信および、写真撮影用のカメラが会場内に入り、客席が映り込む場合がございます。
Also, please note cameras for video streaming and photography will be in the venue, and seats may appear on camera.
喜んでます！これらの映像や写真は、プロモーション等に使用される可能性がありますので、あらかじめご了承ください。
We appreciate your understanding that these images and photos may be used for promotions and other purposes.
いいお返事！
Good response!
また、ライブの発祥タグは「#星街すいせいライブツアー」のハッシュタグを使ってたくさん盛り上げてください！
Also, please use the live concert hashtag "#HoshimachiSuiseiLiveTour" to hype things up!
アナウンスは以上です。
That concludes the announcements.
大阪の皆さん！
Everyone in Osaka!
イエーイ！
Yay!
ライブが始まる前からもう声枯れそうとしてるんじゃないですか？
Aren't your voices about to go hoarse even before the live starts?
まだまだいけますよねえ？
You still have plenty left in you, right?
開演までもう少しです！みんなで一緒に盛り上がりましょう！ありがとうございました！
Just a little longer until the show starts! Let's get hyped together! Thank you very much!
白いカーテンのsway
White curtains swaying,
似たような朝のようで
like any ordinary morning.
まるで違う 交差する星彩
Crossing starlight, completely different.
新しく目覚める “thinking to myself”
Newly awakening, "thinking to myself."
定型文のstoryteller micは渡しちゃ駄目
Can't hand over the formulaic storyteller mic.
安全圏のobserver error 何を信じる？
Safe zone observer error, what do you believe in?
oh oh 眩しくて 逸らした初期衝動 今追随して
Oh oh, dazzling, pursuing the initial impulse I averted my eyes from.
空の愛の歌ばかりで もう聴き飽きてきたでしょ
You must be tired of hearing only empty love songs.
blackout流星 knock down寸前
Blackout meteor, on the verge of knockdown.
退屈してんじゃない？？
Aren't you bored??
“I'm ready to dawn”
"I'm ready to dawn."
千載一遇のnew senseで想像
Imagining with a once-in-a-lifetime new sense,
光速のsympathyで oh oh oh oh oh
with light-speed sympathy, oh oh oh oh oh.
直感主義のinnocenceで創造
Creating with intuition-based innocence.
奇跡も世界も 自分次第で！
Miracles and the world are up to you!
start to know 革命の狼煙は
Start to know, the signal fire of revolution is
start to go 変化を恐れない覚悟さ
Start to go, the resolve not to fear change.
渇いた大地を駆ける 唯一の光
The sole light running across the parched earth.
変わりたい・変えたい の連鎖が
The chain of wanting to change and wanting to transform
剥き出しの魂を焚き付ける
stokes our bared souls.
6000万年に一度きりのsurpriseでドラマティックなキスにしよう encount!
Let's make it a dramatic kiss with a once-in-60-million-years surprise, encount!
夜空に駆けた 遠すぎる欠片
A distant fragment rushing through the night sky,
光速超え 魅せられまだ覚めない
surpassing light speed, still captivated and awake.
惑星が導くレーダー
The radar guided by planets,
what do you need?
what do you take?
望む場所へと
To the place you desire,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
無謀な夢なら 青天井
If it's a reckless dream, the sky's the limit,
危ないほどアガる high-tension
high-tension rising to a dangerous level.
繰り出すんだ
Unleashing it,
とめて、鮮明で、
stopping, so vivid,
叫び声上げる前の1ページ
the page before the shouting begins...
叫び声上げる前の
Before the shouting begins,
もう1ページ
one more page...
失敗幾度も学んでいく
Learning from failure time and time again.
もうこのままずっと降りやまない
It's rain that will never stop
雨の世界だ 愛するしかない
in this world. I have to love it,
それしかない 昨日じゃないから
nothing else, because it's not yesterday.
そう白紙になった青春の何ページ目だっけ
Yeah, what page of youth did it become a blank slate?
忘れ物の思い出せないまま忘れそう このままじゃ
I'm about to forget without remembering what I forgot, just like this.
このままじゃ
Just like this...
風の形に見えない
You look like the shape of the wind,
見えないよあなたも
invisible, even you are.
あなただって同じきっとなんてしてられない動き
Even you are the same, movements you can't just stay still with—
出すよ
let's put it out,
好みかけてこぼさないよ
casting it so it doesn't spill,
泣いとってしょうがないさ
crying won't help, so it can't be helped.
もうこのままずっと降りやまない雨の世界だ
It's a world of rain that will never stop just like this.
もう悲しくない きっとなれる
It's no longer sad, I'm sure I can become...
生き抜くため そう白紙になった青春の何ページ目だっけ
To survive... Yeah, what page of youth did it become a blank slate?
今君に会いたいと涙こらえ
Holding back tears, wanting to see you right now,
せめてさよならだ さよならなんだって認めたくないけど
At least saying goodbye, even though I don't want to admit it's a goodbye.
雨上がりのこの世界が眩しいから もう帰らない
Because this world after the rain is so dazzling, I won't go back anymore.
振り返らない 思い出とともに新しい風に遭われ
Along with memories of not looking back, meeting a new wind,
そしてまた君に会いたいと願い かけていく かけていく
and wishing once more to see you, casting it, casting it...
かけていく かけていく
Casting it, casting it...
声聞かせてください！
Please let me hear your voice!
気を失いそうで
Feeling like I'm losing consciousness,
深いほどに 隠せない
the deeper it is, the more I can't hide it.
どこにようが 輝くものしか ここにはない
Wherever I am, only things that shine are here.
君は一緒に行っても落ち着かない 痛えない傷でもギリギリがいて
Even if you go with me, you're restless. Even with unbearable wounds, just barely making it,
明日香 いつかきっとじゃ何の意味も知り気はない 確かなどこが示しているのえ
Someday for sure means nothing, no desire to know. What is certainty showing?
いけよ、さかせ、さかせよ、さかせ
Go on, bloom, bloom, bloom!
切るまで積み切る 闇は無限の形
Accumulating until cutting off, darkness is an infinite shape.
旅するわけは 理屈じゃないの 瞬き命をさきほこれ
The reason for traveling isn't logic; blink and let your life bloom proudly!
からにこもって 怯えぬぜにふく かけた苦者たちの
Hiding in a shell, trembling, casting away the suffering ones...
また絶えず命よ さきほこれ
Once again, let your life bloom proudly!
空にこもって 怯えぬぜにふく かけぬぜにふく
Trapped in the sky, trembling...
風はない 受け入れて届く
There is no wind. Accept it and it reaches you.
描きたくしゃたちの夢の音
The sound of dreams of those who wanted to draw...
次に生きたいして何が悪い？本当の敵も味方もおどれって
What's wrong with wanting to live next? True enemies and allies, dance!
ほらめえかい だからしょうきっときょうきで きりきりまいり 次から次へと過去に手を振って
Look ahead, so with certainty and madness, spinning around, waving goodbye to the past one after another.
いけよ鳴らせ鳴らせ胸の鐘
Go on, ring, ring the bell of your heart!
だってもう僕は星だから stellar stellar
Because I am a star, stellar stellar
きっと君はもう気付いていた
Surely you had already realized
僕の心の奥で描いた
What I drew deep within my heart—
それがこれから話す陳腐なモノローグさ
that is the cliché monologue I'll share from now on.
ずっと言えない言葉があった
There were words I could never say,
壊せない壁があったんだ ずっとさ
and a wall that could never be broken down, always.
ふっと香り立つ朝の匂いが
The suddenly fragrant scent of morning
どうしようもなく憎らしくて
was hopelessly hateful...
部屋の隅で膝を抱えて 震えていた
I was shivering, hugging my knees in the corner of the room.
太陽なんていらないから
"I don't need a sun,
明けないでいて
so don't let the dawn break."
その手を伸ばして 誰かに届くように
Stretching out that hand, so it reaches someone,
僕だって君と同じ 特別なんかじゃないから
I'm just like you, nothing special at all,
そうさ僕は夜を歌うよ stellar stellar
That's right, I sing to the night, stellar stellar
ありったけの輝きで 今宵音楽はずっとずっと止まらない
with all my radiance, tonight the music will never, ever stop.
そうだ僕がずっとなりたかったのは
That's right, what I always wanted to become
待ってるシンデレラじゃないさ
wasn't a waiting Cinderella—
迎えに行く王子様だ
it's the prince going to greet her.
だってもう僕は星だから
Because I am a star,
なんてありふれた話なんだ
what a cliché story that is.
理想だけ書き連ねていた
I was just writing down ideals
ノートの隅に眠るほんのワンシーンだ
sleeping in the corner of my notebook, just one scene.
きっとあの星も泣いてるんだ
Surely that star is crying too,
明日なんて来ないままでいて
wishing tomorrow would never come.
その手を伸ばして 誰かに届くように
Stretching out that hand, so it reaches someone,
本当に大切なものは目に見えないようなんだ
truly precious things seem invisible to the eye.
そうさ僕は夜を歌うよ stellar stellar
That's right, I sing to the night, stellar stellar
ありのまま考えないで 今宵音楽はきっときっと止まらない
Without overthinking, just as I am, tonight the music will surely, surely never stop.
そうだ僕がずっとなりたかったのは
That's right, what I always wanted to become
あーでもヒロインじゃないさ
ah, wasn't an adoring heroine—
救いに行くヒーローだ
it's the hero going to save the day.
夢見がちな大人になりたくない
I don't want to become a daydreaming adult,
そうさ僕は夜を歌うよ stellar stellar
that's right, I sing to the night, stellar stellar
ありったけの輝きで 今宵音楽はずっとずっと止まらない
with all my radiance, tonight the music will never, ever stop.
そうさ僕は愛を歌うよ stellar stellar
That's right, I sing of love, stellar stellar
世界宇宙の真ん中で 今宵音楽はきっときっと止まらない
right in the middle of the universe, tonight the music will surely, surely never stop.
そうだ僕がずっとなりたかったのは
That's right, what I always wanted to become
待ってるシンデレラじゃないさ
wasn't a waiting Cinderella—
迎えに行く王子様だ
it's the prince going to greet her.
だってもう僕は星だから
Because I am a star,
そうだ僕は星だった
that's right, I was a star.
stellar stellar
あの黄昏も折り畳めば静寂
Fold up that twilight too, and it's silence
僕らの街じゃ暗がりは合図だ
In our town, the darkness is a signal
灯を消してはじめよう
Let's turn off the lights and begin
幕よ開け 見上げ願いを あなたのように
Open the curtain, look up and make a wish, just like you
変わらず在っていたい
Wanting to remain unchanged
きらめきのヴェールを 目元に彗星描いて
Drawing a comet over my eyes with a shimmering veil
瞬いたソワレ 今だ！
The twinkling soirée, now's the time!
寝息を立てる太陽の目を盗んで 大脱走さ 逃げ出そうぜ
Stealing the sun's sleeping eyes, let's make a great escape
夜が明けるまでさ
Until dawn breaks
もう少しこのままで
Just a little longer like this
あの鐘の音は茜さしたって止まない
That bell's toll won't stop even if it glows madder
大阪！
Osaka!
大きく、大きく、大きく、大きく！
Thank you so much!
ということで、彗星のごとく現れたスターな原石、バーチャルアイドル星街すいせいです！
With that said, the rough diamond of a star who appeared like a comet, Virtual Idol Hoshimachi Suisei!
すいちゃんはーー！
Suichan is—!
いいね。
Nice.
これが大阪の空気！これが大阪の空気！
This is the Osaka atmosphere! This is the Osaka atmosphere!
いやもう始まる前から皆さんの「すいちゃーーん！今日ーー！」って一気な感じでしたよね。
I mean, even before it started, everyone had that rushing feeling of 'Suichaaan! Today—!'
もう聞いてましたよ。
I was already listening, you know.
裏でずっと「女どものーーお前ら声足りてねえぞーー！」みたいな。
Backstage, I was like, 'You girls— don't you have enough voice—!'
いや本当になんかもう始まる前からずっと楽しくて、えー、星街すいせいライブツアー 2024 スペクトルノヴァ 第2公演です！
I really had so much fun even before it started, um, this is the Hoshimachi Suisei Live Tour 2024 Spectrum Nova 2nd Performance!
皆様ようこそいらっしゃいました！
Everyone, welcome!
ちょっと交通、大丈夫でしたか？
Um, were your travels okay?
私ずっとさ、Twitterでさ、みんな大丈夫か？大丈夫かなあってずっとツイートしてたんですけど、今日ここにこられなかったよって人ーー！
I kept tweeting on Twitter, 'Is everyone okay? Will they be okay?', and for those who couldn't make it here today—!
あ、あれ？いやいるいるいる。みんないるの。ここに無事辿り着けたよって人ーー！
Ah, wait? No, they're here, they're here. Everyone's here. For those who safely made it here—!
よかった。
I'm glad.
いや、あのですね、実はあの、前回ですね、埼玉県公園で携帯持って、あの、そこでプレミアム公開の枠を立てたりしてたんですけど、
Actually, you see, last time at the Saitama performance, I held my phone and set up the Premiere public frame there,
今日はここでエゴサをして、辿り着けなかった！って人がいたら、「えーがんばりたかったんだってーーえー！」っていう会をしようかと思ったんだけど、あの携帯を忘れました。
Today I thought about doing a session where I ego-search here, and if anyone couldn't make it, I'd go, 'Ehh, you wanted to try your best— ehh!', but I forgot my phone.
学屋に、すみません。本当に。
To the dressing room, I'm sorry. Really.
ごめん、だから今日はいの！ごめん！え、可愛い？遊んとこも可愛いと？ありがとうございます。いやいやそんな、そんな。
Sorry, so I don't have it today! Sorry! Eh, cute? The places I played around are cute too? Thank you very much. No, no, come on.
ということで、えー大阪の人ってちなみに、
With that said, um, people from Osaka, by the way,
大阪らへんに住んでますよって人はちなみにどれくらい？めちゃいるじゃん！
how many people live around Osaka? There are so many!
ほぼ大阪じゃん！え、大阪じゃないよって人！お、ほぼ大阪じゃないじゃん！あ、そうなんだ。
It's practically Osaka! Eh, people who aren't from Osaka! Oh, it's practically not Osaka! Oh, is that so.
いやいいですね、楽しい。
Well, this is nice, it's fun.
はい、ということで台本をめくって…なんと皆さん、先日発表したんですけれども、ついに武道館ライブ決定しました！
Right, so turning the script... As you all know, I announced it the other day, but finally, a Budokan live has been decided!
ありがとう、ありがとう。
Thank you, thank you.
新しいアルバムもね、出ます。えへへへ。
A new album will also be released, you know. Hehehe.
あ、実は、あの今日のね、ここでの公演で、実は予約できたらしいんですけど、ここで予約したよって人！お、めちゃいるーー！
Ah, actually, at today's performance here, it seems reservations were possible, and people who reserved here! Oh, there are so many—!
お、ありがとう！なんかね可愛いやつがついてくるらしいからね、楽しみにしててください。
Oh, thank you! Apparently, something cute comes with it, so please look forward to it.
そしてバンドさん！ジャカジャンジャカジャン！はい。セカンド、そして埼玉県公演からの引き続きの皆様でございます。
And the band! Jakajan jakajan! Yes. The second, and continuing from the Saitama performance, everyone.
ありがとう！来てましたね、ありがとうって。
Thank you! They were here, saying thank you.
そして配信ももちろんあります！
And of course there is streaming as well!
わーー！えー、ここにこられなかった人もね、いっぱいいますからね。いや、見てください、すいちゃんのこの可愛い姿を。え、な、どんなポーズしたらいいんだろ？切れる？切れる？可愛い？え、指差す？
Waa—! Um, there are a lot of people who couldn't come here too. Well, look at Suichan's cute appearance. Eh, wh-, what pose should I do? Can you cut? Can you cut? Cute? Eh, point?
ピース！凡キャブラリー少ないですね。アパティコ？
Peace! My vocabulary is a bit low, isn't it. Apa-tiko?
ピース！
Peace!
そして韓国でのライブビューイングも行っております。
And we are also holding a live viewing in Korea.
アンニョンハセヨー！
Annyeonghaseyo!
イイデスネー
That's great!
はい、そしてライブの感想はハッシュタグ#駆け巡る星町でたくさんツイートしてください！
And please tweet your thoughts on the live using the hashtag #KakeneguruHoshimachi!
はーい！
Yeah!
え、YouTube、TikTokでご覧の方は
Um, for those watching on YouTube or TikTok,
ここまで！
That's it for now!
この先を無料でいられると思うな！
Don't think you can see the rest for free!
そうだ！
That's right!
ぜひね、概要欄から配信サイトに飛んでぜひチケットを買ってください！
Please check the description, go to the streaming site, and buy tickets!
買ってー！
Buy them!
はい、今回はですね、もう埼玉公演から実はもうセトリが違うんですよ。
Yes, this time, the setlist is actually different starting from the Saitama performance.
気づいた？
Did you notice?
実はセトリがもう違うので、もうここから先はもっとセトリが違います。
Actually, the setlist is already different, so from here on, it'll be even more different.
さあ、何を歌うのかお楽しみに！
Now, look forward to what I'll sing!
無料パートは終了いたしました ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching.